Seino, Galgal Channel, go go go!
Yes, today is a summer project!
We are going to do Nagashi Somen together!
That's groundbreaking.
I read that as groundbreaking.
Have you ever done Nagashi Somen?
Yes, I have.
Have you done this too?
I haven't had the chance.
Opportunity, you don't get to do that very often.
With real bamboo.
Oh, yes.
When I was little.
Today it's just the four of us, in a set that feels like summer.
This is amazing.
It's cute, isn't it?
So cute.
We're going to do Nagashi Somen!
Well, let's just say it's a good thing.
Well, that's right.
You can do Nagashi Somen.
It's moving somehow.
I'll push it here, too.
It's moving!
Oh, wow!
That's great!
Water is flowing!
Jeanne, it's somen noodles.
Let's do it.
I'm worried it's going to overflow.
Let's get everyone out of here.
Leave everyone behind, Mr. Toana.
Let's not leave them behind.
What? I can't eat it.
I won't give it to Toana-chan.I won't give it to Toana-chan.
Aaah!
It's so hard!
You're eating a lot!
Yes!
I'll have some.
It's so good!
Isn't this fast? This.
No, it's pretty fast.
Delicious!
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Want some, Momo?
Wait a minute. I'm having too much fun flushing it.
Why?
I'm going to become a sinker.
It's going to keep flowing.
Momochan, it's flowing fast.
Everyone, take it hard.
Bon appétit.
It's delicious.
Hoi!
Oh, everyone is surprised.
Hey, don't take it.
Where is it?
Already.
You're early, Mr. Sink.
Maybe I am.
Don't tell me everyone's posture is slow.
I'm not.
Good luck.
Can I eat this tomato?
I want some.
Let's flush the tomatoes, too.
Oh, is that what you mean?
Let's flush the tomatoes, too.Let's flush the tomatoes, too.
Yes, that's right.
Then let's flush them.
The other way around.
Smilla, Spalt.
It's in my stomach.
I've been eating all the way down to my stomach, now.
Let the tomatoes flow, too.
Let the tomatoes flow.
Isn't it hard to catch?
It's okay, it's okay. You can do it.
Everybody, everybody.
Okay.
Oh!
It's flying so fast.
Whoa!
Wah!
Aaaaah!
I'm out.
I'll be so mad if I go here.
Yes, the zone. I'm sorry.
I'm angry.
Oh, I can't grab it, these tomatoes.
A lot of tomatoes here.
I want to grab it.
Oh, I can't grab it.
Put a lot of them.
Oh, I can't grab it, these tomatoes.
What should I do?
It's too fast.
Wow, great.
Yay.
Um, they're going to pour it all out.
Please do.
Are you okay?
He wants to do his best.He wants to do his best.
Eh?
I got him to do his best.
He said he wants to be a sink.
Oh, really?
Can I have a tomato?
Yes, you may.
Let me know if you want some.
Yes, I do.
I'll see you here,
Okay.
I'll see you in the comments on YouTube,
Yeah, very good.
I'm going to show you some of the emergency episodes of the summer that we've been looking for.
Yay.
Okay.
Well, first of all.
When I was in junior high school, I went to the beach nearby with my girlfriend,
We were both gazing at the sea in a daze.
Wow.
It's cute that a boy drew that.
Indeed.
I'm sure.
We never looked at the ocean when we were in junior high school.
No, you haven't.
No, I haven't.
This is not summer,
But when my boyfriend is coming home from school with me.
I've seen him hold my hand naturally when we're walking home from school together.
Wow.
I love it.
That's so cute.
He's saying it's summer.
It's so cute.
It's summer.Summer.
Hey, I'm going to get angry.
When the hair of the boy I like is parted in the center
When his hair is parted in the center.
Oh, you usually wear it down?
I went up and dried it off.
I was like, "Cool.
I like it.
Nice.
Wow.
It's summer.
He told me I was sweating after gym,
He gently wiped me with a towel that smelled like fabric softener.
Eeeee.
He wiped me off?
What are you doing?
I thought he was wiping me off.
He wiped me.
He wiped me up. Oh, man.
That's not good.
Does that mean I'm sweating?
No, you might laugh.
What? I was just thinking.
It's some kind of cartoon swimsuit.
It's a cartoon.
It's from a comic book.
Everyone says it's summer.
There's nothing but excitement.
When you fall from a high place, your heart starts to pound.
What's that?
It's a swish.
It's not a squeak.
It's a heart-crunching crisis.
It's that the person I love let me use his towel.It's that you let me use a towel that someone I like used to use.
I guess towels make you squeamish.
Do you carry a handkerchief with you?
I do today.
I know, right?
Rolling up the sleeves from short sleeves.
Almost no sleeves are cool.
I'm sure there are people who do.
I know you're here.
Here's a curly one.
Do the "twirl, twirl, twirl" thing.
Oh, I see.
Maybe there are a lot of people who do that.
There are.
In the gym?
Yes, for sure.
Summer episodes around me.
It doesn't have to be a summer epic.
Summer episodes?
Summer epi?
Cicada.
Maybe you haven't heard.
You're lying.
No, that's not true.
It's not summer without cicadas.
Oh, okay.
Shall we noodle?
Shall we?
You want to spoon it?
I'm going to spoon it.
I knew it.
I've been quiet all day.
Sorry.
Misaki's got one.
Take it.Take it.
Let's do our best, the two in the middle.
Sure.
That's pretty good,
It's difficult, isn't it?
They'll come as soon as you put them in.
Are you okay?
I'll open it for 10 seconds.
I'll call out to them, and then I'll let them in.
Like, "Here we go.
Oh, "good boy.
When I say I'll let you in, I'll say, "Good-bye.
"Good boy.
I'll put it in.
I'll say, "I'll put it in," and you'll say, "I'll put it in.
I don't want to put it in.
I say, "I'll put it in, I don't want to put it in.
I'll put it in.
Good idea.
More and more.
It's all mixed up.
I couldn't get it out.
You can't get it out.
He said it's too early to give up.
I'll put it in.
Here we go.
Don't lie to me.
I don't like it.
Tomatoes are beautiful.
Always angry tomatoes.
I'll put it in.
Good idea.
No good.No.
No, no, no.
I won't tell you if you can't get it yet.
Here, try to make it hard for yourself.
Okay.
I'll go.
Here we go.
Excuse me!
Um, um...
Is it okay?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
What just happened?
Thank you for the somen noodles.
Thank you for the noodles.
It was delicious!
Many Q&A episodes
Not summer Q&A episodes
All at once
I got it.
I felt like it was summer.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Summer Project! Yay!
Yes, so this time we will be doing fireworks with these 4 guys!
Fireworks
Well, I was so loud that a lot of people went to see the fireworks.
I didn't know that.
That's really funny.
Are you the type to do fireworks every year?
No, but we did last year... as a family.
Oh, you did?
We did it as a family, so I'm glad we did it again this year.
Really?
I'm glad you're here.I'm glad you see it this way.
Yay.
That means there's a lot of attention.
Let's do fireworks.
Here we go.
Together.
What?
The fourth one's a little different.
What's that?
Let's do it.
This one's better.
This one?
This one's better?
This one's better.
Come on!
It's green.
Wow!
I can see it!
Did you guys get it?
Yeah!
It's so close, it's like...
Ya!
Yeah!
Oh, here it comes.
It changes color! It's changing colors.
Wow!
Oh, my gosh!
It's so beautiful.
What's that?
So beautiful!
Oh, my God!
Let's see, you're early.
That was fast.
Is this it?
Oh, isn't it beautiful?
This is it, this is it, this is it.this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this
Ha-ha-ha.
Yah!
Wow!
Natto!
Wow, it's so long!
I'm done.
Did you get to the bottom of the bowl?
Wow, that's a lot of bees!
Oh, my gosh!
It's beautiful.
Oh, here it comes.
We're in it together.
Are you scared?
Scary, but beautiful.
Oh, it changed color.
It's the one you were holding.
It's so beautiful.
Well then...
Mi-chan, what is it?
What? What?
We're here.
It's just the four of us.
It's a picture of love.
That's nice.
That's why I gave it to you.
LOVE.
All of you.
Squeeze me.
Hugs. - Hugs.
Oh, oh, oh,
Here we go.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.Oh, no, no, no, no!
Oh, it's gone.
It's gone.
Okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Ta-da!
Fireworks!
This is a showdown, right? It's a classic.
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you.
This way...
Wait, you sound like a beginner.
I've done this before.
All of you.
Ready?
Oh, here it comes...
It hurts, I've got a cold, I've got a cold, stop it!
Oh, I think I'm going to get a cold...
Clear's here, too, and it's getting heavy.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Kira's stepping on it!
You're doing great, look, it's connected!
Kira's doing her best. - That's great!
Great, she did it at the same time as Mimi!
Yo-ga, watch out, it hurts!
No, I got here too late.
I was late getting here.
I'll take it. Congratulations.
Congratulations. You were a little late getting to Yo-ga's.
That's it, isn't it? This is difficult.
The start... I guess that's part of it.
So which fireworks were the most fun?
Which one was the best? And the first one.
I know. You see them in TV dramas.
Yes, but yes.
It's my hobby.I guess this is my hobby after all.
Let's do it again sometime with all the members.
Fireworks... with your family... again.
I'd like to. I don't know.
I don't know. But I would like to do it.
Thank you for watching!
If you liked this video, please subscribe to our channel, comment and rate us!
Bye bye!
This time I'm wearing dholic's costume!